JALILOV SHAKHZODKHON

TEXAS · +6037503361

jalilovshakhzodkhon@gmail.com github.com/shakhzodkhonjalilov shakhzodkhonjalilov.github.io/portfolio

FRONT END developer with three year experience in Web Development, I follow the news and study everything related to the web.

Experience in building application architecture from scratch.

Knowledge in programming: data structures, algorithms, server-client interactions.

EXPERIENCE

11.01.2020-11.05.2021

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER, INSURANCE COMPANY MSK ISHONCH

- Development, refactoring and support of projects on Vue, Wordpress for the Insurance industry:
- Tech support.
- Development of a platform from scratch with registration, statistics, purchase of an online insurance policy.
- Technologies: VueJs, Wordpress
- Optimization and improvement of project architecture

Technologies: Vue Js, Express.js, MongoDB, Socket.io

06.20.2021-04.01.2022

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER, THE CYDIO GROUP INC.

- Development, refactoring and support of projects on React, Wordpress
- Worked on a development team which included other technical professionals, subject matter

experts, project stakeholders and executive leadership.

Developed web applications with a focus on, but not necessarily limited to, the frontend implementation.

- Development of a platform from scratch with registration, statistics, purchase of an online insurance policy.
- Technologies: React, QA, Wordpress
- Optimization and improvement of project architecture

Technologies: React, Express.js, MongoDB

EDUCATION

2018-2022

BS IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

Tashkent State Technical University

SKILLS

- GIT
- Troubleshooting
- HTML,CSS,Javascript,Vue.js, React
- SQL

- Wordpress
- Mongo Db
- Node JS (Basics)
- QA

LANGUAGES

Russian

English

Uzbek